Um, I know that I know it's sick
I didn't know what I was looking at and I just asked if he's
I don't and he was that wasn't even his picture. He was using in the first place. He was
And then he showed a vegan page. He's not supposed to I said no doxing and then he's like doxing
he doxed just
They said bateman and then vegan patriot and then
A bear that poor bear is now getting pizzas delivered to his house
So I don't I don't know
I just write I use it. I don't wait too much. You can deal with right now. I go Andy
My god one after another
Like I posted a sex oh he did see
So why are you telling me the long dog? Why are you telling me that it wasn't a sex screenshot?
Triple X I
Know you're trying to chill chill again. I know it was just I mean I
Prefer like you know you argue with him rather than like you know some other stuff to happen, but yeah
Like I'll post it a triple yeah
Well, I'll post I mean, I think you know fuck
What is it? He's lying to me. Oh, mr. Big. All right now. I can't check it
It's like someone someone has a picture of what happens if there's a bear or not
It just looks like a penis to me. It looks like some kind of ended. I was just a weird
This is a weird timing. Hey Tommy James
Bear catch you a fish in his mouth. I don't know
It's like me just like you these are normal fixtures, please
Well, so if you I don't think you're with we're really good sweet sweet mo, okay
There's a screen seven minute triple X video was this Tommy saying
Well, I think I heard vegan patriot has the only fans. I don't think it's the secret
Okay
I don't know. Well, it's it's gone. Whenever it was it's gone. Whatever it was
I asked him I kind of did ask him I was like, can you not you just put up a normal photo because I didn't
know with the first photo he did then
That's a photo. I think it was Jason Bateman or then
That's what if it's being patriotic and then he puts a bear in a fish. I
Just don't know I think it's a little I just have to be the absolute
Sometimes you have to be a little bit paranoid because sometimes people are trying to do shit to you, right?
What's there? Yeah, I don't disagree. I mean
Yeah
But no one is bigger big like dude no one no one like if there is anyone that came close to how fucking awesome
I am I would be like dude, hook me up. Let me hang off as much fucker
Please
Like is anyone anywhere like if anyone thinks that they're a shred like please
Hit me up my DMs. Mr. Big Pipe's
Healthy self-confidence is a good self-confidence and healthy, you know, I'm a little bit
More self-depreciating I think but yeah, I like I'm very humble. I am day. I'm so fucking humble. I'm so fucking
Okay, Brian, well, I understand
I think there's a lot of sexually frustrated people that come on the panel sometimes
They've act out
Talking to my blackout
I'm sorry, it's Boston, it's Boston, not Brian.
Beach, sorry.
Who are you talking to?
Oh, no, no, there's Brian in the chat.
You're talking to my fucking child of vodka, fucking F-slur.
I can't say it.
What's the thing, I got, I'm gonna say it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm gonna get your fucking vodka,
fucking vodka, I'm gonna call my fucking vodka,
fucking fuck.
Okay, let's welcome to, hey, Paige, it's so,
Hanging in their page, you know
Alice is gone page Alice is gone. I've uh, I've been a page page
Can't play pretty songs, right?
He would he like he wouldn't say another sort of character. Actually like dude pages like check out actually fuck
Sorry, it's monkey
Uh, yeah, play some stocks for paid. I'm sure she's like every everyone likes there
I'd say like every single chick I've ever seen associated with this shit. I wouldn't have sex with but yeah page
I probably would
Yeah, you know, I did it. You can't you know, I did is because he started talking about like 90 women
That I'd be like pass, but yeah, it's kind of hot
Yeah, guys, you know what it's because it's not
People that are so interested in a wrench it's like really like, you know before I was like really like relaxed about like, you know
Policy and so but it's really I get any really need moderators to be on my side
And so I think if they're not either that I need any
Pages nails like shit. Can we get page like fucking really fancy nails and shit
Well, cut page has a show it's called prairie page and wildflowers and you can go into her chat and and discuss it with her
Okay, I don't I don't know if she wants to
Discuss it in my chat
Okay, but how to get my fucking camera
You got the back words pipes it's women who should oh yeah, well mr. Big Pipe said he did was attractive women
But then he said he thought
No, I didn't say that I like literally showed you pictures. Yeah, I know I
I've seen that very attractive, but you thought you were like you said you were
Broke you know you I remember you being attracted, but you said you were shy or something like if you can't believe you were getting them
But you were yeah, I mean like cuz I'm like
I don't think I'm myself as like
Some like sexy hunk or whatever
You're kind of a hunk
Let's see
Women like I don't know what that looks like. I'm like, I know it like what like aquaman and like the rock or whatever
But I don't look like that and so like
God damn
Think of and like just like through like I never even like took my clothes off like just through like chilling and shit
Yeah, I'd be like so like you want to make out now or like
Well, I mean it goes sometimes yeah, yeah, I've made out with people my life. Let's see
Yeah
No shit
I'll fucking kiss you. I'll fucking kiss you.
Let's make out a little bit. You're gonna be my first fucking you're gonna be my first kiss with a man.
Wow. Wow, that's sexy.
You want it? You want it, bitch?
What's your straight tongue?
I don't know if I like it. I don't know if I like it.
Okay, well you can just try it once.
I mean, I'm trying it. I think I'm trying it right now, but we can try it with over the internet
I can't even see your face. It's the same way. I try it like with anyone
Well, thank you
Let's take a shower you cuddle
Fish dude, what the fuck I do
I mean you gotta take a shower take a shower and then most cuddle
Okay, well go clean the piss. I'm Joe from the corner of your room. You motherfucker
Anyway, mr. Big Pipe is banned from the show. So anyway
Guys, I take a shower last night. Oh
My god
Don't be said Jedi you mr. Big loser hikes, okay?
your big
Dork sir big
Sir big pookie. Okay, that's yours. It's a big pookie from now on, okay?
Anyway, I miss you big times
Not a message of pleasure knowing you you're kind of a big douchebag. Nobody likes you. Anyway, enjoy your life
Okay, a grown man to make out with the dot horn Brian because big pipes had to make a point on something
He made out with his dog. Wow
Yeah, that's that's unusual. Mr. Big Fives. No, Mr. Big Fives, you're gonna you're gonna like
Try to like you're doing exactly what Alex did. I don't know if you're trying to copy Alice or whatever
He's trying to say the same thing. I don't feel like being degraded and you know, maybe
I said a whole thing like about me on my show like, you know, I
Don't know if you don't like me don't watch me, but it's I don't feel like talking to you right now
You know, I do permanent bands, but you know
Sometimes they go insane and talk to the person again. We'll see what happens
I can just say you guys are just showing you're just revealing yourselves. God. Thank you so much for letting them reveal themselves
Guys, I wouldn't have this guy on for a lot long
I would have had him on like all the time and fucking from over his channel and and been a supporter instead of music was good
I would have done that over and over again. He has to be nasty to me, right? It's okay. It's okay
I've been called I've been called worse by better people. Okay, so
Yeah, this is a big pipes pisses in a jug in the corner is a room
Okay, and so and then he's talking to me about I smell okay. Well, whatever. I don't have any piss jokes in my room, okay? I
Have a wonderful natural odor
There you know, you brought you said it you said it like a roulette. Oh, uh, that's you smell like this good tickets that way
Well now I don't feel like making out with you anymore
Jimmy Tom
There's not a bit of cash anywhere
You guys are just I
What is what are you waiting? What is the deal? It's like it's must be Alex
Yeah
Yeah, it's a big five. Yeah
Why it's like it's not like
It's just like, you know, you're you can say something nice
Oh, we can joke around but then it's like you just take it to like this like oh
Well, you know, but you're disgusting freak and I wouldn't I don't think I would ever do that
So you said so
It's okay
I don't smell bad the point is I don't smell bad and you're like me gets it seemed like I'm some kind of like smelly person
I'm like not
I smell fine. I use spirit water. I take a shower every day. Maybe I miss a day occasionally and I
You said
Hey, smell like fish. I think it's sour. You just take a shower. Okay. Well, let's look at page things
But I'm just I'm just you know becoming a punching bag for the entire entire community of frozen
It's like, Alice turned on me, Mr. Big Pipe's turned on me.
You know, everybody's, well, Alice was, he said earlier, he was like, oh, he's like,
is that a real nose?
Your nose looks fake.
It looks like you can take it, if you're not on it, but I was like, no, I had a nose
I had a I had an original when I was 17. Oh you didn't you know there's a thousand that how much did it cost?
There's a thousand dollars. How'd you afford that you should have spoiled you like a little spoiled discussing animal
Like you know, you're you're you live in a disgusting pamphlet like well
It's not I was like it was just out of nowhere and then I saw it as the I blocked them
Yeah
And and and also he said the f a g g o speak twice like and I told him not to say it
Then he see I said I've been shall you promise not to say it
He said it literally like a minute later as soon as soon as he came back on
I guess and it's like and I have to start with my streams because people are like, you know
Looking for any like little and think to complain about on my show or two
Okay, um, Mr. Big Pies, let's rewind our conversation and it's like and then you kind of said the same thing
You know, I'll maybe let you on the show some other time
Mr. Big Pies, but I just I've had a rough night and I just can't take it anymore with you
He's not sorry and it's like and the way he said it is kind of like just
the same kind of weird way I was the same thing and just like saying
It's like trying to be mean for this thing to be mean or something. I don't I just it was just out of nowhere page
I'm not
All I do is, like, say, can you please respect the rules in the chat?
Can you please not say this, because you're not done?
And that's all I've said.
I didn't, they act like I've, you know, like, done this horrible thing.
I didn't do anything to them.
OK, yeah, come back later.
Come back in another time, Mr. Big Five.
It's just too much tonight, you know?
I'm not in the mood for music anymore tonight.
He didn't apologize to be to either and you know, he kind of downplayed that you know, I you wouldn't even do it as a favor
like I
Don't know. I'm trying to make it try to make peason though. You're thinking about a different
Okay, I don't know mr. Big Pipe when you say I smell it mr. Big Pipe's just that oh
He's like you like you want to make out I'll make out with you
He's like, but you take a shower first you smell like fish and
Bet you really yeah
Well that maybe that was part of the it was like part of the joke or something, but it was just like
Yeah, it was just that he was just annoying he just that he's
Just annoying tonight. He like sometimes they can appreciate
Appreciate it. It's like not the night for I also had a really
Crazy earlier panel where I just got all these trolls from all these places come in and there's nobody in the chat
I even knew people were like not respecting me in the chat and then
There's they're all fighting on the panel. I think I think you might have walked in cuz I saw you say hi everybody
And then it's like we probably walk right out when you saw it like we're on the panel people are just like
saying horrible things and stuff and
you know
I know you're trying to chill mr. Big Pies, but
No, just chill in the chat. You can chill in the chat. Okay, just chill in the chat. Okay
Chill in the chat. I'm talking to the Ms. Page right now
And I don't think I don't have pages in the mood for being serenaded by three songs right now
Honestly, I don't I don't it's your pet. I don't care who you have. I'm not in them. I'm not fighting with nobody
I don't really care you guys can ever do you want
Okay, no, I'm gonna say it's just that's a big pipes trying to come up and he wants to sing you a song
Do it was like that or
I don't care, sir. I don't care. Yeah
It's a big time
Special request
I want you to sing a song. Can you sing a song? I want you to sing a song. Can you sing a song?
And sing it to me, sing it to me, sing it to me, sing it to me, sing it to me, sing it to me.
You know what, Jimmy, Tom, I don't know you, but I would like you to shut the fuck up because you don't know my fucking life.
And I don't really want to talk about that, nor does any of your business.
But no, I support myself, thank you.
Whoa, your finger is shaky, it's fucked.
You know, I'm stressed right out. I like I really bad shakes have nerve damage and I'm just stressed right out
I've been having like anxiety tax panic tax all fucking day, and I can't get it to go away. So I'm not sure what to do
Yeah, but HK he just he disrespected me too, but you know what?
I like neutralize the disrespect you feel you can apologize to me you can apologize also to beta and then you can
Dude, you gotta you can't beat it. You can't be that predator and then homeless. Okay. That's what happened
Oh my god. No, I did
Yes, you did and that she was very she was mad at me for weeks about it
I didn't kick you off immediately. Can you please just apologize for saying that?
Like, number one, the situation has been handled like fucking three or four times already.
And it's like, it's weird. It's disrespectful to me that it keeps getting repeated.
Okay, well then just leave you shouldn't probably like if you feel disrespected in my chat
And it's like you probably should just leave because the chat is kind of like turned against you worse than they have on me
So hey, so what's going on? What is happening right now?
I'm trying to chill like I'm trying to be cool and show I swear to God like whatever I can do to be chill
What's going on? Nothing. I mean, it's like I just I just I told you I just I just I just took him off the panel
because he was being like really rude to me and then
But I wanted to you know bring him back and like we can you know, maybe have
He said he wanted to sing a song. He didn't want to sing a song and so I was like maybe
Wherever you want to play he said you had some songs to play
I don't know. I'll play a fucking pretty song or some shit. Okay. Go ahead. Hi, Pico. Hi, really, Nancy.
And I depended of high, high Australia.
I got five out of ten.
Shooting both stars, but I couldn't make it. Didn't make them down, but I couldn't make fish.
I hope you go. What song is this?
Oh, it's fucking shit.
I'm going to do it.
Thank you.
Saki, did you like it?
I like it.
Did you feel something?
I want to play pretty shit.
OK.
See it from your heart.
You have the talent.
You just put the soul into it, OK?
You're doing your thing.
Saki, I love you, Saki.
You love me?
Motherfucker like how many shots how many shots of vodka do you have tonight mr. B price?
I'm probably I'm like fucking me 15 now, but okay. Well, you've had too much vodka that day when you fall in love with me
That means you've had too much vodka. I'm saying
If any motherfucker, I mean real if it's any motherfucker try to hurt you and my presence and we're chill
Oh, okay. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Thank you. I appreciate it. I know you're gonna say thank you so much. I appreciate you protecting me
Thank you. Just hit him with your guitar
If anyone but bothers me, okay
You're a fiddle and throw your kazoo at them. Okay. I can care
What what's wrong? I'm the new mr.
Mr. Lemon
This is a pretty part.
I'm saying, don't give up, it's been a long time I've been here
two
Um, we're in the chat. What do you think or the panty?
Was that a god damn penny dropper? I think it was
Well
I think everyone said the panties are firmly firmly still on
I said maybe you need to like I don't know maybe fix your audio that I don't you might want to look into like someone said
So I like am I playing like a fucking like
No, you play you play you play it fine, but it's like this microphone is not picking up like a lot of the sound so it keeps breaking out
So it's like oh you said you would you're playing well, so it's microphone. I
Didn't turn off the fucking echo cancellation
Let's see
Okay
Like these killers I like I hang out with like killer felon piece of shit and I beat the fuck
Thank you for being on the show. I mean, it was wonderful. Thank you. Thank you so much. Oh, yes
I don't I can't take any more page. I'm sorry. It's too big pipes a little bit. I didn't hear what it was said
What's that? What did I make fucking thing cut out? Oh, sorry. Oh, you know, he played a song and then
He was like saying he didn't beat up people in a mental asylum
I don't know you say he's just uh, he's rambling a little bit. I was like, uh, I kind of had enough
Thank you for the song though, that was beautiful.
Been an edgy day for sure.
Yeah.
You know, I'm sorry. It looks like you've had maybe had a tough day. I hope I hope you're doing okay
Like I'm sorry to drive you into like any negative of your draw. I know but I know it can get like Harry here
I want to make you feel bad. I'm supposed to like make you smile right now
So like I'm coming in here thinking all just gonna be very much some shit. I just need a distraction
I just like need to not think about anything right now. Okay
Well, if you don't want to think then I'll have this a big pipe back because yeah, dude
I don't know why you kicked me man
Like he'll take you. He's talking completely off. That's a little
Like dude, I'm just here. I'm a human being I'm trying to show
Tickling me just a human being
You're turning on an alien it's a big pipe you're an alien
Maybe.
Maybe?
Well, you're a bit of a banjo-playing alien.
I don't even have my banjo.
Hey, what's that page?
A book?
Oh, yeah.
Oh coloring. Oh, you're a coloring book. Oh
I think I think it's like the Thunderbird on the front it's under bird tribe Hicca. I've heard of the Thunderbird tribe
Is that ours now? Let me see. Oh, that's a thing
beautiful
pretty
I need some practice go my yeah
Yeah, I'm via
Everyone everyone you're a big friend of fruit. Hey, I'm crystal like a mobile panel like crystal
I just you can't say at page. Yeah, I think it wasn't that you it wasn't that I'm offended about it
It's just like I just don't want the word said for the algorithm and stuff. That's why I am in that show. I'm not
I'm not mad. I hope you're not mad at me. You seem like you're like irritated at me like I wasn't saying I was talking about you
Or that I was joking. I was joking about you. I said that and that's I like you mentioned
I just said I sometimes joke when I tell stories and so maybe you got offended
OK, so Crissel has had that book page.
Crissel has had that book.
Remember?
Are you going to get back to playing guitar?
Kind of play it like.
Play it as you're playing.
But do this kind of background music.
Because Paige and I are having a discussion.
Yeah, we can only play it softly.
OK.
No.
Head to head.
You'll never join again, Crissel?
OK.
Bye.
I didn't have the time, but I'm living in a high house, living in a high house
I feel the past
I'm trying to take who's that it's still on like he's
Okay, don't feel it
Have a nice life
You can join Alex and
Okay, I'll give mr. Big Pies out in a few minutes. You can still be in the chat
Part time do the pretty part and do the free part. We're waiting. I'm reading
All right, this part's pretty
Where to go like this part's actually really pretty
Mamma, säg
Janka var
I school
Kan peke
Vad ser ut bära dig?
Jag tjatar
Jag mår väl
Nej, väger
I had a hard time, I was really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really
Who's gonna be that woman who's half of us?
Yeah!
Well, that's the first song you played.
Oh, that's it. I like that song.
It was a song.
I hope.
That's great.
You like that joke?
Oh, no, it's a song.
I like this song. I'm sorry.
I like this song.
Hey Paige, you wearing panties?
Hey
I'm just like this is part of like the fucking
Listen lady fucking hang on them cuz I'm about to fucking blow your panties off
Oh
Women put their panties back on around you when you
Take a pair of underwear and a pair of
Like wrapping a present what the fuck
You're reading a book mr. Bigpipes a coloring book
I'm like
I'm so many puns deep
Just give me the fucking pussy
Shit
Cheers, bitch
Oh, you're a pure
Okay, you're you're gone you're gone. I don't know what that
I was just gonna ask who the fuck he was talking to you. I didn't realize he was talking to me if he was oh
Like oh, I hope he wasn't talking to you. I mean maybe he's talking to me
But I really don't wear panties and big pipes and and page is not interested in the super fights
I can just tell I can tell you she's not interested. Okay, so leave her alone be creepy
Okay
I know
No, no, just like not not like you think
Well page he kept he kept calling you bitch and then he said he was gonna
Yeah, then he said this is something about punching somebody and so I was like I don't know issues. I said no
It was rude being rude and then he was like, hey, are you in Panties page?
And then he's like, I would unwrap that present and then you're like, what, present?
You're like, I'm wrapping your present.
He's like, I'm so many puns deep.
Just give me that pussade, that's what he said.
So you just talk like him?
Yeah.
That's what he was saying.
Yeah, he did get a little a little out of hand there for a sec. I just caught
But I didn't realize he was talking to me. I thought he was talking to someone in the chat
So it's like well gonna ask him if he was talking to me and then you kicked him off
So now it's all settled we're good
Yeah, well, I'm sorry. I don't want to like
I'll creep you out. But yes, he was talking about you. He mentioned you earlier tonight. He was like, where's Paige?
I need to talk to Paige. I would totally date her. Hold on one second. I'll bring him back.
Dude, I don't know what you're talking about.
Mr. Big Pansy, what are you saying?
Like, be specific about something and then discuss the topic.
You just said something, you were saying, you said, you said, are you wearing panties?
You were saying, did my son blow up your panties?
And you're saying, I want that pussy and he called her a bitch.
So, Mr. Big Pansy, did you say that?
Like, if you're wearing panties, hang on to them.
Because, like, when I play my banjo, I'm gonna blow your goddamn panties off.
Oh my god.
Okay, okay, well, okay, I thought you were saying something about, okay, well, I don't know if that was, I don't know if that was really possible.
It's just like, you know, what's that?
Like cross your legs, lady.
Oh my god.
It's just right now.
I feel like such an old person tonight.
Oh my gosh.
I feel old too. I don't know any of this new bingo. I don't have all this internet social media work
So I'm just like this old man trying to do this stream. I don't really know what I'm doing and
Blackout Andy came on and said you're a very good streamer. You know you need to do and I was like
I'll give you a little hint of advice
anything blackout Andy tells you to do the opposite and then if it works like
think you're doing the right thing
yeah so yeah
he's a little trouble maker
damn i just play sick blues you want to hear some sick blues right let's go
like i can play some sick fucking blues let's go
Well, I can do the sickest blues. Yeah, I can do the sickest blues the one I could even think of right now
But I got a tune
So the standard that one's a F
It's a fucking a so I got a harmonica. I just played f-chord
What's going on here if you got
Brother give it to me right now. I want it
um give give to you motherfucker i want i think i paid these things okay i do think what i'm not
going to do it on here oh i would love i'd love a duet someday with you mr big pipes and maybe
i we can have it we have a triplet we can i can i can do some background vocals too that'd be great
maybe not okay page is like no big
Big Susan. Oh, you know, oh, oh, oh, oh, Susanna. Oh, don't you cry for me?
I'm going to Alabama with a banjo on my new
I'm gonna put gel packs if they never fucking work
Hi Chris though, we're having a concert, we're having a concert, your microphone's too low,
hold on, let's figure it out.
I'm too loud
Microphone's too low
What's up, what's up, Mr. White
No, dude, do you like the music? I'm crystal
He's got to play a couple notes together
He says he's from st. Louis
Can we get along together?
Do I have to sing another blue song?
Honestly, I'm going to give you, I'm going to be honest.
Behind these old clothes.
I've known Chris Marie for like eight years and she is a Psyop.
She is like the Daniel Davis.
She's doing that Joan Rivers impressionation
Joan Rivers
So are you are you a beta sex kid robot saying that we met each other eight years and I say
We just met each other.
Yeah, I was like, babe, you're so good at this song.
You're so good at this, John Rivers.
Crystal, would you ever date Mr. Big Pipe?
Or have you?
Absolutely not.
I would be a sexy bitch.
You sexy John Rivers bitch.
Aye, aye, aye.
I was just trying to have fun.
Yeah, yeah, aye.
Yeah, I had fun.
Let's pray out
There we go
We're gonna get our girl singin' before the end of the world.
Maybe I'm a bitch, where are the two?
Song.
Okay.
Hey Raven in the chat.
Raven's here in the chat.
You're awesome.
Maybe I'm a bitch, where are the two?
Oh my gosh.
You cannot do this.
This is nuts.
Are you serious?
BABY I'M AMAZE
So the big one is you I think that first the first option was I think it's high that she's got like that
Crystal can you sing maybe maybe I'm amazed maybe I'm amazed yeah, that's all
Can you sing some crystal? No, I will
I don't know that song. Baby M.M.
There it goes.
Oh, by what artist?
By, tell me what artist.
Hey, this thing is it.
This thing is Baby M.M.A.s.
Hey, who sees Baby M.M.M.A.s?
I mean...
Look at the music in the background.
Okay. Yeah, that was a great song. Okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Mr. Big Five, here, okay, Mr. Big Five,
I'm gonna move you,
it says Mr. Big Five,
we can't hear you, we can't hear you,
Oh
He's saying it tonight, but can you fix your audio and then I'm flash your camera and I'll let you back up
I think the dude needs to make his own channel if he wants to be in the spotlight
He has one he has when he was
But Arthur he's
Don't be
Listen to music. I'll go to Spotify
Spotify. Well, yeah, but I like you know, I like having oh, I like having original
Music on the show, but it's like it's just like his microphone is kind of bad
He's a housing musician. It just can't doesn't pick up right on the microphone
And so it doesn't it's not as best as it could be. I know it's like no dude. I'm not like
Okay, okay
I got a microphone. Okay. Perfect. You got how you doing there Pat? Oh, you know the issue is like the yeah
Like that could cancel it so it's like if I'm gonna play something I can do that really quick
First of all, I see you over there at Zegas. What's going on, man? Why were you no never been there did be over there crystal?
Crystal crystal
Sleep man. She's awake. I think so anyway though anyway though
Yeah, what's your fucking point, dude?
psyche
Oh, you tried to make a channel like a YouTube channel or some shit
I know it's late, you haven't been live like you've been in the past couple of weeks.
I've been live almost all day, today I was almost all in it last night.
It used to go live more often though, honestly.
I'm thinking of lessons more sometimes.
Maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you so much, maybe I
I'm trying to play my listening to this guy on fucking panel
You know when you're in the subway in New York, and you're trying to go get your subway
Notice on YouTube, because I know I used to be on panel with another dude who would always play the guitar.
There's something about guitarists that are musicians.
that they just need, they're hungry for getting feedback.
Oh my god, that was so great, that was so great.
Did you play this song?
It's something about them.
Usually most guitar players actually call guitars Pussy Magnets,
and I think that's why they play.
the
Yeah, let's do it. Let's do it.
Let's fucking go.
That is fucking beautiful.
That's fucking sweet.
I love it.
Hey, I thought you, uh, you've been busy.
I'm like, damn. Dude, you sound dumb.
I don't, like, I will never, like, you're laughing
to happy and like my fucking shit
I will never fucking...
I thought you were busy. I'm like y'all just figured it out in your life like you used to so I'm like remember you told me you told us that that one day you came over here too and it's like it's something like you always came over?
I did DMC recently, yeah. It's legal to do it, it's legal to smoke it.
It's really yeah, it's at least because they can make it you can make it out of this bark
We just make it yourself. Yeah, there's a bark
Oh, bye. Shout out to Sam in in the chat. Hey, did you hear me fucking play that fucking Beals shit?
That's kind of cool. Oh, it's Beals. Okay. Yeah, Crystal. If you come back
It's a fucking goddamn Paulin burning his baby of a maze by the Beatles crystal. Oh my god
You got Maya in the chat
Okay, empty guitar case in high school for the girls that I hurt my hand and it worked
Oh the loser. I told you pussy man. Even the gutter guitar case is a pussy bag
I'm gonna need to play guitar. I just have a case
Look, I'm like me sighing
Yeah
Loser, we have a thing that is member. Thank you for being a member thing that is appreciate that
Ivy
I'll add you name to my book. I'll have to add you to the book Arthur a page
I already added to the book you're on my thank you
I think I have some
Pages on a page
I just like honestly like a bunch of fucking like this one fucker like the biggest pretender fucking retired ever
Yo Pat, I'm gonna I'm just in a real dude. No, I don't like shut the fuck up. No, like you sound like vomit. Oh
My god
Question
Apple belong on pizza
What wait, why does it or does it or just or or doesn't I'm asking you does pineapple belong on pizza
Only Canadian bacon
That's fresh. Are you okay? Are you okay? Mr. Big Fives? I heard a scream
Hello
Hello. Oh, no, it's oh, I just
My foot
Going there Chris. Yes, please drop someone's panties. I was waiting. It wasn't waiting all night
Are you doing there beautiful? How you doing? You're my manager
I'm your band. Yo, I saw you at Zayas. What's wrong with you? Come on, man. Nobody's over there anymore. Why'd you call in over there?
Well, because I had you know, I don't have for all these years. Oh my god. Oh
You're her friend
Thank you. You learned not to be a dick. I'd rather you take you out
I don't want to be disrespectful. I don't want to over-speak.
No, you're fine. No, no, no. You're gonna have worse.
I know Mr. Big Pies. He's just like,
he's like a merry-on to stay at the restaurant.
He's live on his channel. He's like, cut the bullshit.
Nobody's here for fucking music. I've got fucking four in the morning, bro.
What the fuck?
AI, AI, you gotta be my manager now, okay?
I gotta have some...
Okay, here. You didn't like it. You didn't like it when you were there.
Thank you for not getting me there.
Hey.
Are you going to do that? Are you going to do that?
Are you going to do that?
Are you going to do that with Crystal?
You're just saying maybe I'm amazed with Crystal.
I want to hear.
No, she won't.
What did you say?
Can you sing Baby in a Maze?
The Beatles.
I love that song.
I know you love it.
I don't know about it.
I don't know, Papa, I don't know.
Chris, Chris, guys, guys, guys,
Chris Hill is just Sandman's drag character
if you haven't figured it out yet.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my God.
I'm the one that is so Sandman-like.
I'm the baby of my maids.
Listen, I only...
Hey, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to see my, I don't want to
I'm in the real deal.
Yeah, yeah.
Crystal, Crystal, Crystal, Crystal.
Crystal, you're just, Crystal,
you're on Sandman's panel saying,
oh, I'm like the, I'm like Sandman's other half.
I'm like the female Sandman.
And then you just said you're or something like that.
And so they, I made a little joke.
Oh, look, Crystal's just Sandman and drag.
You know, it's obviously not true.
We know you're not Sandman and drag.
It's called a joke, okay?
And then you come and call me.
or not, you know, I don't care if you call me that.
Just don't say it on my panel, and you say it again twice,
and you're in a hateful way.
You won't get a third chance.
You're gone.
Yeah.
And you don't vote.
Sorry.
Alex, Alex is already outside the studio.
Maybe, you know, maybe you could get over with it.
You're a fucking spellbag.
What do you say?
yes how am i threatening am i talking to me right guess what am i confused are you talking to me
i just got government official you get deeper you want brother i can fucking government official
you with that bullshit bitch what the fuck are you on about does anybody understand what the
fuck she talking about send me a pizza you faggot how am i threatening anyone send me a pizza so
Purposely without me fucking you over January what the fuck are you talking about?
Yes, we don't need no nothing don't need no gang life
Government I told you I'm sorry. I'm confused. I'm trying to follow
You're jumping on me for no reason I didn't threaten anyone
Oh, because I said there wouldn't be a third time now. Just fucking around. I mean, you shouldn't say it at all
It's breaks you ass. Yeah, you're hurting his piano. Yeah, I'm not threatening you
You're gonna make a claim you gotta back it up
Yeah, I'm a can I play the rest of the fucking baby. Yeah, play play we're all listening
it's good that guy's never gonna get away with fucking threatening
I've never once threatened you and if I did threaten you please explain how I threatened you
Cuz you're talking to me right you threaten by the government you said that T. Why guy that's me
How do I explain okay? I'm not gonna I'm not gonna keep asking you the same question explain how I
Go ahead. Don't say my I say please explain how I
Does somebody's house you want a government official pizza fuck are you on a psyche?
Do you even understand what crystals saying cuz I'm honestly confused
It's like, can you please explain her position to me? I don't know
I mean
He said do you want to have a pizza delivered at your house today?
The government got you
You're fucked oh my fuck you do this you are
Buddy, yeah, they got your mommy's address. They got
You know, I hate to say it but I'd rather listen to the music than you first. So that's how crazy you are
I don't know the fuck you're talking about
Well, guess what?
I'm not going to guess nothing with you.
You're crazy.
Then I can fucking make it fucking federal.
You fucking weirdos.
You want to threaten people with pizzas now?
You want me to threaten you?
I'll do it now.
Yeah.
Please explain what you're doing.
It's a federal offense.
I'm gonna send the pizza to your house.
And it's going to be a final problem.
There you go.
Ha ha ha.
You've done so well.
You've got to pay for the pizza.
Pay for the pizza.
Oh, those take it back.
Okay.
Jail seems to say, hold on.
Y'all swear as well.
I know it's Jail and Mike.
They're reported by Harsh.
Look at that over there.
Oh.
You're up. Oh, yeah
I can't tell they say the end word all day long though. I mean it's like I don't I now Lisa's channel is
Said like on the donations and stuff. So I don't think it's like unless people are like really like reporting it
But I just have people like put it up for my channel. So I'm gonna have to be careful. It's not necessarily
Are you I think step it's just are you threatening me?
Shaking me
Yeah
Do you not know do you not know anything about me? Well, you just figured it out
I don't know what the fuck you're talking about. You're not making sense. Hey
Unfortunately, you're just threatened an employee of NASA you are. Oh my oh shit. Oh fuck my bad. I like to take this time to apologize
I'll apologize to NASA my bad
Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt Dirt D
I love my maize that the way I make me feel and I'm gonna buy Crystal Pizza I'm gonna leave
off the pineapple then extra garlic and extra pineapple please.
I'm going to send the same crust pizza with the extra cheese on it.
Okay, brody.
Crissel, do you know the story, guys?
No, it isn't Minecraft.
This is a video game channel, guys.
So...
Crissel, I want to hear you belt out.
David, I'm amazed.
You see?
Baby, I'm amazed by the way you look.
Awesome for that Justin Timberlake. What the fuck? Yeah, I know my
You're the song. I'm sorry, you know
You ain't nothing but a ham dog
right all the time
That one is a big place
Sikey, I have an original. I can sing it to you if you don't mind. Okay. Yeah
Dom dom dom
Nothing but a dom-dom-dom a little bit of
I guess I keep
It's original
Kind of a little bit repetitive
Little bit, yeah
Let me pet it up though. Mr. Sam. Mr. Altai is always okay. Come on. So be nice to Mr. Big Pets.
Can I write a song about those?
Yeah. Yeah, go ahead.
That's not it. Like, you want to start over?
No, just play any music. Crystal's gonna have a good freestyle.
Are you gonna actually fucking sing it?
Yeah.
This is our freestyle song.
Papa, just fucking play, dude.
I see ghost is trying out. No ghost ghost ghost is like the least I didn't do anything bad
He didn't do anything bad. You didn't do anything bad. Nobody's like I feel like saying certain words
I'm not even trying to do that because
You don't even know what does she don't even know where the fuck she's at. Do you know you're at personal?
you know where you're at, buddy, do you know where you're at?
Yeah, I do. I do. Yes, I do.
Yeah, you don't know where you're at. You don't know.
Yeah, you're making a claim, but if you're going to make a claim,
you're going to have to prove that claim.
I know exactly where I'm at. I was just asking if you know where you're at.
All right.
I can tell that you guys are fighting.
I'm not fighting. It's not even a fight or even talking.
All right. I'm going to blow your pants off.
Okay.
Mr. Bigfoot, no one's panting to blow up all night.
Oh my god, not again.
You know what?
Blow my pants off and we will drink some more quiet.
That bad idea.
Oh my god.
That's fucking cool.
I'm a man.
I don't know.
I don't know the song, dude.
Oh my god.
I can't stop laughing.
I don't know what the fuck he's talking about.
He's welcome to join.
Oh my god.
I don't know what the fuck he's talking about.
We're going up the scale, okay. Oh my god. You're very high up my ears. My ears. There's a break
You're high
I mean the guitar is working for you
Is it really?
It's not, guys I play way better than he does
The guitar sounds good
This is his pants he's dropper saw or your panties
I'm not wearing pants. I'm not wearing pants or underwear
Play a ship
Baby, I'm amazed at the way you love me, oh, hey
Yeah
You play better
I'm not a lead
I did not see it. I was, I was, um,
fortunate enough not to see it.
I wouldn't like to.
You wouldn't like to?
Yeah, go ahead.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
Yeah
I have no idea poison. I have no idea. I don't know those people are
does does yelling does yelling
I
Are you drunk or tired or an hour and none of you both me
Now it's talking to her
Hey, hey, are you good?
And I've been
Yeah, you at this point brother, come on. Okay. Okay. Okay. I'll interrupt. I was talking to him not you
Yeah, I'm saying that music's gonna be
But mr. Because you keep playing the thing
Like no different song like why it was fun like the first couple minutes it was
Makeup something else like why can't you like just make up a new song like I can make up a he said he made up a new song
And it was exactly the same
Revenor actually like women are starting to put suspenders on their panties so they stay up and they don't fly off
around you know
On the panties. That's the first time I ever heard that. Hey, you like that idea?
You know what you know what psyche that was you sometimes you come up with a good one and that was kind of a good one
I will
No
By the way, psyche
the
No, because I know they're not really in my like I think they're in like I think they're in like other places like
They are but technically you can see them from like America when they have when there's like a solar flare or something like yeah
If you like living Alaska
There's recently
Nobody probably more prominent in your area, but you can see all the way from like north
like North North America like sometimes it like extends further because you know
But you never see that shit if you're like from like Florida or something like you would only to see if you're from like like fucking
Michigan or something, but you can barely see it's nothing like being in like Alaska or nothing. That's not what I was saying. Oh
Because that's the only place I could only
That's the only place you could what I'm sorry, so go ahead
In America. Yeah
By the way, I just called you sweet
No, like
Yeah, we were trying to like talk it and it's like and you're like talking over us the same song. Yeah
No, like, uh, give me the time so you weren't talking over us. You were singing over
us. No, he's specific about it. So that, like, less, less, less, less hour, less hour, less hour.
I mean, not for an hour. The same song. The same song. He gave you so many chances. Of what?
What am I doing?
Play a different song.
Yeah.
I just want you to stop singing.
I wanted to see one pair of panties in a chat
or the panel blown all the way up
and there's not one.
Nobody.
Okay, go ahead.
Girl, take them panties off.
Oh, sorry, never mind.
I was just kidding.
Maybe I'm amazed and whatever the last one you're seeing is
Loop a loop for hours. Maybe I'm amazed. I know I don't like
It's like so many times
Okay, I will mr. Dumb pipe. I didn't know that was real. Oh, mr.
First time and then the last four times were really why is he playing the song? It's okay. It's okay
That's a robotic ass voice
Talking is it robotic for you to psyche
We're gonna get the moment mr. Big 5 says the music is making all the women hot and bothered the women need a break
We're getting
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry about the headset, Alex sent me equipment.
We're all going to get jelly.
Oh, but what, soccer?
So, I had to find an old headset and duct tape it together.
Hey, that's that dude might be country
I had the red green it
Good guys, why are you just like flip-flops down there? You're wearing a loincloth. What is the oh?
I think
Oh, hey, hey, hey, whoa, whoa, brother.
Oh, whoa, brother.
I've got to watch.
Yeah.
I've clipped our phones before.
What's the deal with the liberals?
Try, baby, pussies.
Trying to show us a little something.
What are you talking about, Mr. Everybody?
You're being weird.
What do you think?
Oh, shit.
Good times.
Dude
My first interaction with good times since I was in Michigan two times
Good times, and I have to work on actually I actually I had Intel I got Intel
until I get
He's like I'm afraid to hang out with mr. Big Pipes. No, I never said that I said I did not want to hang out with you
He doesn't like your pipes
I mean look at the way you just came at me motherfucker come on
Why did I show up there next year?
Oh
Good good times. He's he's being patriots managing mod. So he's pretty much the highest horse in the universe. Oh my god
Yeah, good times like fucking I told vegan patreon to go fuck herself
Yeah, yeah, she said she was a meth addict. She's smug man. I have a washer-sense
I've been good times worse nightmare good times and pipes and crystal they're they're on like
It's hard to keep up with them. They're just so like
I'm not gonna talk shit though. Are we actors? Are we better?
No, you're not if you can act this good, you know, I'd probably tell you a little bit
I think you're honestly generally
Dum-dums. Can I say dum-dums like you?
Just stab my eyeballs, bitch.
No, he can't.
Alright, what do you...
Is this a horrible thing?
No, go stab him in the gum-dum.
I didn't say horrible things.
Well, say gum-dum.
You better say egg-dum.
I say gum-dum all the time.
Get over it, Chris.
Would you like to debate about me saying gum-dum?
You better say gum-dum when you say dum-dum fatty.
No, give me gum gum because you're a dumb dumb. That's a better argument. I'll make your argument for you
Okay, yeah, please find out finally
I'm so sorry guys, I'm so sorry guys
You look like an adult Haley, you look like an adult Haley Joe Austin, like exactly, he's been really kind of my sister, you're like 300 pounds and you're like Jesus mile, right?
I honestly thought that was Paige in the background, I'm not gonna lie to you.
And it's fucking Mr. Pipes going off again.
Is that Paige singing? Paige is right there, she's just singing.
Paige sing this one.
No, I'm not in the mood for this one.
He keeps moving her around where are you in the mood?
Well, I like if you would move we could you move paid in good times next to each other? Thank you.
Thank you.
Hey!
Well, sorry, you put me up there for it.
This is wild. This is wild. This is taking pictures.
You want to do it a good time.
I love good times. I want good times to find somebody that loves him.
Good times knows that I care about him as a friend.
Nah, we weren't chilling for a while earlier and everything was chill.
Well, do you know that Paige finds you very attractive, but you just...
Nah, I don't make her feel uncomfortable.
Oh, sorry. Sorry. Sorry. I mean everyone likes I guess everyone on this panel likes to make a page full and comfortable
Then when I defender, I'm caught a simp in a white knight. I don't know
Especially against Alex well psyche when I even allowed to say that
Did you benefit you yeah
I was wondering, he would not tell me that, and he started saying horrible things about me, and then he called me really bad names, and they'd say, uh-huh, he should have known all about me.
So, like, all you gotta do is, like, if you would argue with him, bro, he don't know what the fuck he's talking about.
We both love you, good times, we love you, good times.
I'm just happy I was able to find a headset and make it work.
I love you overall.
Yeah, we love you, Fred.
Is your first name Fred, good times?
No, it's not.
What's your last name is William William? Oh, sorry. Oh, sorry. No, that's fine
Everybody already knows everything about me. I don't give a shit I
Would never call you William good. I'm good times for life. That's what I go by on streaming stuff, whatever
Good times, we need a celebration.
Hey, good times. May I ask you one question? I'm not trying to be rude.
What's the point of your... Dude, stop talking. Start singing. Shut up.
Hey, uh, good times.
What's the point of your green screen?
I mean, you're green.
Like, what is that?
I
Crystal names yeah, yeah
Hey listen, I'm Mr. Big Pipes, I just shredded your fucking panties off for each of you.
You guys hear what I'm saying?
He's spreading my panties.
I barely hear it.
I didn't do anything to his microphone, that's his microphone.
What?
Like you want well, I don't care. I'm down to psyche. I'm down to talk to the man
But he's probably gonna try to fucking say something
Really good friends and good times is like one of those ones that like
Like sit on something and like
Will fucking make you fucking pay later and that's what we mean psyche are really good friends
We have fish tacos together believe it or not
We don't do anything. We just say, but on the pier. That's where we did it.
I always say the words for good time.
So he's doxxing.
I can't. I can't all the time. It's not a good time.
can you call me ghost and uh not first of all because first of all first of all sounds so familiar
i didn't know that he was i think i did pistol i was it was pistol yeah i know but it's so
similar sorry okay i thought you i didn't know that good times go call me don't don't thank you but
i really care about good times my whole life uh like he told me that he had cancer four times
Why is this dude still in the panel either let him join or let him leave he's like halfway he's like in like
You want to join or do you want to leave
But it's always there though, it's like
right by your ear
your fucking asshole a part
nobody hears anything no everyone said that nobody hears anything
i don't think he's here
my good times is getting to you later on
we're just hearing things
do you see his ears
i'm so good
they're on the
they got the fuck out
look at my head
now he's dead
hey doors
I
Don't care where you go
For what I've admitted everything about my life
Who are you talking to
Yeah, who the fuck are you talking? I'm gonna know he's sorry because I'm not
Nobody that's around the fuck with okay. I don't think it's here. Yeah
Well, yeah, I have a little bit of the same message to your girlfriend.
I can figure out how to put a headset back together.
Motherfucker, come on.
Yeah, I'm making sure it's accurate where we see it, so.
I'm not gonna mess with you, but I know that shit don't feel good. I know that shit's rubbing against your skin, by the way
I can't hear him because his mic's so loud.
I don't like to talk about you, good dog.
You know, that's like, you know, I don't like you being nice to me, but I still don't like you being a fucking mean and I don't like people being mean to you.
The crystal I have a question TY one question. Do you feel like I was being mean to you at any point tonight?
Yes, I do and you're okay. Can you explain how? How do you feel like I was being mean to you?
Yes, cuz I would like to apologize
Okay, go ahead. We go Michigan. I got mr. Big pipes gone. You made it. Yeah, mr. Big pipes. I'm gonna leave now
Yeah, I
Okay, yes, sir
Okay, well deems her what I would I want to talk to you. I'm I'm not right to have pipes is back
All right, Crystal. Go ahead. I can't get pipes is back. I'll listen listen. I don't I don't know pipes are right now
Okay, I don't know him. I don't know. He's poop. Do you remember the question? I just asked you
I know it was kind of confusing
No, I think I said did you feel like I'd expect you to know because I'd like to apologize. Yeah. Yeah, exactly
You kept over-talking me and you kept doing very wrong things and very mean things.
I did not.
That was a meanie.
That wasn't me.
I just joined like
Oh my gosh, dude
It was you to save my head work. I haven't when Vita was up here and I had itself
Okay, well, therefore you're a fucking liar. You don't know what you're talking about because last time I was on here
And beta was up here was like, it's like he was that you know, it was it was
Nice about her. Oh, are we up here the other night? Or are you saying I just I was talking about tonight
If you want to talk about the other night or the in the past about it. I was talking about tonight. It was tonight
Okay, I'm sorry
Hold on. Yeah, just join those definitely just join
Ada wasn't up here
Crystal is this safe to say that
Are you and I'm asking this because like I am drinking I'm not gonna lie to you
Are you under the influence of the anything right now?
Absolutely not. I do not do drugs and guess what? I still remember it
You're kind of like are you just
Can I ask respectfully are are you on the can I even ask that are you on them? Are you in the spectrum?
My third one's gonna get worse, but are you on the spectrum or not?
What I didn't expect you I didn't expect you to answer that are you what my third question is are you a dumb dumb
Types
You can go three versus one if you guys want, let's run that bitch.
Um, they better get the white one though.
Good times, if you ever say dum-dum,
I'll never say dum-dum.
Yeah, exactly, you're gonna ignore the point.
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
Can you just...
You're too stupid to make the point.
Too much of a dum-dum, which I called you up when I first died here,
and I'll show you, nice.
I'm, this is me not even crashing out.
Okay, don't ever do that either.
I'm not even crashing out.
I'm saying not the weirdest.
And the weirdest you don't even know what the fuck you're talking up a crystal. You've said you haven't said one thing that made sense
Well, because this guy maybe I met you in the past, but you cannot you've not said one thing
I don't give a fuck what he did
You don't understand
Hey, Chris. Oh, you just god damn you have a little Chris. Oh, please and I hate to say this
I'm a Christian. I
I
Hope you're on something because if you're this fucking retard it. I mean, I hear this dumb dumb
There's a problem. Okay a growth and straight up 30 says dumb dumb, okay?
The dude in his 30, I don't know how Duke in his 90s can say dumb dumb. If you're talking dumb dumb
He's gonna say it dumb dumb now. Don't you want to make an argument now? I'll forget all your past
What would you like to let's win it
This guy's so retarded
Crystal you're you're on another you're on another plane of existence. I mean come on now
Like come on
This guy you got to get this guy away from me good times. Tell him I can't do anything leave
Talking about listen, here's the one thing I've learned from joining panels. I know you don't give a fuck, but I'm gonna say it
When I'm not, especially if I'm not smart enough or anything to understand, what a man does,
he shuts the fuck up and he listens.
If I was a woman, I would just leave and then I would shut the fuck up and listen and learn.
I mean, you mean good times, what's good times gonna do?
He's a fucking dum-dum too.
This is not my time you can bring up. You can bring up pipes. You can bring up one night
I'm only page alone, but you can bring up all three of you. Let's we can run it. What do you want to talk about?
I'm trying to be nice
Hey, but you don't know where the fuck you are. You're just you're like that old fucking drunk lady
That is like breeze to having she's got keep this respect the fuck off. That's a good argument. All right
How am I disrespecting you?
I just enjoyed I don't know what's going on. I heard 20 push-ups by the way in the background
How am I this is like, you know, I don't mean it. Oh shit
God good times good brother
I'm just trying to understand
Oh my god since I'm a female I'd never been all the way like this
But I talked to the males like this dude. I talked to good times like this. I thought the pipes like this
I thought that what we're not gonna say all these other names
But I thought there was one like this
You're not going to talk to all these other names like that.
Who? Name one.
Name one. I'm not going to call you.
Did you see what he said?
No, you made the claim to burden approval.
Name one name. I'm not going to call you like that.
I heard you and you're about to get caught.
Name one. Stop fucking talking to someone.
You're not going to talk to all of you like that?
Who the fuck is Audi?
Oh my god, I'm done.
Alright, have a good night.
Goodnight, good night.
You're done, you're done.
I'm not leaving, I'm just done talking to you.
You're done for good now.
You're good.
I'm done for good.
I'm fucked.
You're fucked.
I might have spilled a little bit.
Yeah, I'm good. We will. So,
this is my little friend. He's
my little friend. He goes.
He's always, he's always a
little light for me. So, it's
not so much. Give me good. Give
me good. Give me good advice,
Paige. Uh now, Paige, we're
going to associate with you
because you're bringing her
Why oh
She might give you a card reading but don't give her advice don't hang out with guys this guy is such a bad person
This guy is a bad human. Well, you made the claim. How am I scared to me?
This guy's never been challenge of your views ever in your life
We got you we got you mean we who's we got you bitch
You want to play games we got we got a part of the group dumb dumb. What do you mean?
you mean the retard that's singing or the dumb dumb that's in the fucking books
like I'm not joy I mean I'm proud to be country I'm a redneck all right I'm
country too I'm redneck to you know Bruno I'm also not fucking retarded though
I mean I'm sorry no do you know Bruno I do know I knew I anyone you're about
Haha, that's a brag!
All these questions I asked you and you brought up Bruno. That's how you won and if if honestly, that's what you say
Yep, you deserve to be over there because you're too fucking stupid even have the conversation
I have to say it like that. I have to be you
Are you scared of Bruno?
That's what you took from that conversation
Yeah, he's scared to burn his wife, yes, I love his wife, his wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife, wife
Let's see answer my question
How did I lose I
Keep asking questions you don't answer
It's like talking to you know, I'm gonna leave you alone because honestly you are I don't know if you're drunk
I don't know if you're anything you might be honestly
I might be talking because the first time I was talking before you start at the end you might pause once in a while
All right, don't worry about it
You know, what do you mean fucking? What do you mean? No, what do you say?
Simp, you know, you know, does she doesn't sound retarded to you because I'm sorry
I don't know how she is. I've seen her when she's talking to her now dumb dumb when I talking to her now
He's know me for years
Well, you're both are dumb dumps
That's why I said I take all three well, you know what? Thank you for that compliment. I appreciate very much
It's not a compliment dumb dumb you ever come back to that one
What thanks for the compliment when I obviously I gotta learn didn't give you a compliment
Do I have a comeback for that if do I come back for you speak a nonsense? No, I don't have a comeback
I got facts. I got logical arguments. Yeah. Oh, no bad souls. I know how to deal with people. Hey, Paige
Well, yeah, I guess I could like a chat forgot about that chat's going wild tonight
Oh my god
Can't go we so like added like at what time?
Yeah, I can at like at Fridays and like fucking
Yeah, Chris, so we're all connected we have a conspiracy against you we're all against you I know everyone I'm not against
Even people you see on the street, we're all against you, but I love Crystal.
I'm not against you.
Thank you guys.
Fucking skits are firing at us.
Who's against you?
I'm not even against you, believe it or not.
But I know you're not going to understand that, so I'm not even trying to explain it.
Like I said, I'll be quiet.
Am I bad psyche?
Yeah, you're fucked.
Oh good, oh good.
Baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man, baby, I'm a man
I know this. I see him. I mean, I am here. I've been with you.
What's he doing?
We love it. I mean, we gotta appreciate the small things in life. Come on.
Ah, like mowing the grass and gardening.
And pipes and we're listening pipes
Marie Ken McDonald's is a fan. I know I can McDonald's
McDonald's is my fan anymore. Oh, I love Ken, but he said it. He said are you
Ken McDonald's I love you. I love you. I love you. He must be a big fan
Now he comes
I love him so much. I
think about him a lot I worry about him is like he's getting older and you know
he's a family man I'm gonna come out there don't don't show the pages
she has she has she has got you know you're not show up
oh my god what's going on he said he was he said he's gonna go visit you in Canada I'm like don't
I don't want to hang out with you and you're your trespass from my property. Take about that one don't ever go
I'm not terrified of you. I
just don't like you. I think
you're a dickhead retard. Oh
shit. I mean, you said it,
brother. Well, I know it's like
actually say what you thought
though. At least you said it.
Yeah, that's what I was
I could not hear him at all. What is he talking about?
Oh, good. You just walked in here.
He turned his voice. I think it's like he turned his volume down.
I know his mic is messed up because his volume is like halfway up.
I'll turn it all the way up on him.
Here you go. Mr. Bighead, can you talk?
No, please don't.
I won't even pay to him. I can take my headset off.
You're muted. Your microphone sucks, my friend. I'm sorry.
You know I'm not even allowed here. You're allowed here used to know you. I didn't ban you from hell. You're allowed here
You're here right now. Well last night after or the other night you like beta in
Flirty Diamond got into a huge fight and then you out of nowhere said Crystal is not allowed here and I was like I don't even thought
Well, I don't remember. I thought maybe you said something and I took off the panel because you said I because they can't say the f-a-g-g-o-t
Like I don't I don't like that. I just don't
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Sometimes I
Mixed up mix up a panel. I'll mix it up. I love I love you
And I love you good times and this would be privacy. Okay, and I hate page
After she gave me that count down and I don't like love. I don't like I love it. I love it be that I don't need fake love
I don't want fake love dude. Oh, I know
Explained what fake love is
I mean, I mean, I mean, it's like, no, it's not like I, it's not like I want to eat your kitty cat. I mean, it's like, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just, I just,
Yeah, I think that's a good that's a good time. Yeah, he did he did it to me
He was sitting there. He was saying that I was like him. I looked like just like him
He kept saying I don't remember saying that I would say that
I got it on video. It's on video. Okay. I want to take the clip. I want to take the break. I think you look like
Okay, well it's on video. You don't look like you. All I said is that you're like a gorgeous, stunning, beautiful woman and you're
You're fighting a cruel way. That's not what you said. That's not what you said. That's what you said.
I think you look like Joe Sprech. You said you heard that I was a crack.
or bitch and I look I did not say crystal you are lying crystal you are just making things up
I want to see it show the video I need to show the video I want to see what I said that where I said
that I want to see where is it I don't talk I don't talk I don't talk I don't talk about it I don't
talk about it I don't I don't call anyone crack words let it load oh my gosh you did it
so I don't I don't I don't think other people were saying things I didn't say anything I don't
I love it, it's not my vocabulary crystal
I don't know what he's saying, it's not my vocabulary
He was also saying different vocabulary out of his fucking gesture and saying that
He was saying that
What'd I say?
Well, he's throwing me way up
What?
Are you guys
Why don't you guys, don't look at that guy
He's pulling it out of her
Did you get that in the book?
I want to see the video
It's on video, it's on video
I'm sorry
I want to see it
Are Tam calling you a crack war?
Is that what he said?
Yeah, he's called me all kinds of names.
He's called me all kinds of names.
Psyche called you a crack whore.
Yeah, he called me a bunch of different names.
I never once heard him say whore.
I never once heard him say crack, but I mean...
If you got proof, go ahead post it.
We'll listen to it.
Are you sure you just not...
Come on
I swear if I said that I'm so sorry, but I don't
Buy that I'm gonna watch tomorrow. Are you are you a crack or it really I've never done a drug in my life?
And it really are my feelings
Why didn't say it so I don't know you talk. Yeah. Yeah, I came from your man
I'm offended by that and you said that I was like him you said. Oh, there's Kim
Is that Kim in the background or is that crystal in the background? Oh, no, that's Kim
Who the fuck is Kim?
You said it's that crystal Mary
You don't like
Okay, I want to see the clips
Arthur thank you. Thank you, Arthur. Why night Sam?
Such a fat as so bros. No, we're just are my fillings. I didn't
Watch that mouth. I don't give a fuck what you watch you better watch that mouth. That's what you better watch my boy
I don't give a shit
Fuck that summer community over there. You're over here now, bitch.
I don't give a fuck. I'm here now. I don't give a fuck where I came from. I'm a good fuck. What?
Like, go ahead and make your argument. What the fuck are you talking about?
What up, boo?
Order a du-duh.
A du-duh.
Can you get that clip?
Yeah, good name, you fucking dumb dumb.
Yeah, but watch who you're talking to like that.
They can do the grown-up bands. I don't give a fuck. I am a grown-up man
I don't give a fuck where you came from. I don't get fucking the sombers community
I don't give a fuck. It's a psyches community. I'm gonna fuck
You are dumb dummy you don't make
Watch your talk. Do you like that? Oh my god my feeling dumb dumb. Oh my god. I did try to hurt you feelings dumb dumb
What are you man falling another man dumb dumb?
I'm a grown-ass man. A fan is another another man. Have you ever have you ever let's follow your logic?
Are you a fan of football or sports or at all? So you're a fan of another man, aren't you?
You fucking dumb dumb. You don't the fuck you're talking about don't try to come at me cuz I'll bring that ass up
I'm a grown ass man calling you a fucking retard, I don't give a fuck who does, I call a woman a retard. What do you mean? What's the point? What's the argument?
To shut up mother's dog. You were bitch. How am I a bitch?
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about you're too. Yeah, you you've been around
I
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about you don't know you don't even know what you're talking about you might have been there
He was so fucking he looks so fucking miserable he's a fat slump of shit
Fuck it. We'll go fuck it. We'll go for a three four against one fucking on down. So what are you saying?
You're one right
So you actually crystal this shut up
So I've heard you're so fat you go ahead dirty
Yeah, you're so fat you count as three people one two three four five four against one
Are you that fucking stupid you can't even count we like that shit in like kindergarten?
But I said like you're too stupid fucking stupid to count because you just try to say I didn't count right but there's five
Yeah, you did five people up here
Four against one
Crystal stop talking let us talk. Let's have the conversation
That's a good argument you fucking record rest my case. You try. I'm not leaving nowhere. You're not gonna
Crystal's shot you not know crystal sometimes it's okay
You should be quiet and she should be quiet
Yeah
Okay, what's your argument retard? You just try to bring up some more chip fucking break
Are you stupid? I literally have to help you guys with your fucking arguments, and I'm tired of helping you
My logic because like god damn why should I ever have like it especially if you're following a person like this and like
I want to see everything your phone was fake.
I ask the winner we help you do your own fucking argument.
You can talk all you want and you can mumble all you want.
But no one gives a fuck if you mumble and talk.
Just because you're in a panel, you sound retarded.
It's okay to talk to people dumb dumb with a problem.
You don't even know what the fuck that means.
Oh, sorry about that guys. Sorry are Chris. I'm talking to him. Can I talk to the dirder? Do you mind?
Crystal, are you are you on this for are you cheap yesterday?
Definitely not. Are you gonna follow you fucking dumb dumb? I would be these are dumb dumb's beat as fucking boy friend
Even though I've every time me and beta's ever been on the panel together. I've debated her every single time
and I'm I like her and I follow her go ahead and you know what you you hey you
made the claim to burden of proof is on you what you're not gonna make but how
am I how am I a fan of her I got it every time we talk every debate I got
on you buddy it's not a good answer that's that's not an answer can you
please answer my question
Where's somebody using your your image on this word?
How does that answer my question dumb dumb see you guys are moving?
Why you don't like to be to see it you don't like to be you don't like to be out the baby
I know I went I went every time especially gets a fucking retard like you I went every time this shit is literally this
Dude, you're such a f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing s***, bro.
Fat, slunk of s***. Okay, how am I fat?
Go ahead.
You don't see me on camera. Go ahead.
I didn't call you fat. I didn't make the claim. Go ahead, brother.
I've seen you on camera. Okay, let's close.
And how am I fat?
Hey, can we read one of those tarot cards and see how much you weigh?
Hey, don't change the subject, you fucking bitch.
You're gonna come up here and fucking try to challenge me.
I whooped that ass again.
How many times is this, by the way?
You fucking dumb dumb.
How many times do you want me to whoop that ass?
I'll do it again for three.
How many times?
Oh my god.
We were gonna talk the page now, but you came up here talking to me.
Did you not?
You come up here talking to me?
Yeah, I told you to shut your fucking mouth and you're not listening.
Yeah, and I proved why I should be able to talk.
So why don't you shut the fuck up and not talk to me?
Stop burning that ass up and you know better, that's why you know better, that's why you know better talk to me like that, Der Der.
Why'd you do that, sakey, sakey, sakey, sakey, I'm gonna crash out.
Anything you want to talk about, you know I'm fucking, I'm honestly, I'm honestly the smarter than you, you're fucking tart it.
But you honestly know better to talk to me like that, stop burning your ass up on me.
You gotta stay up properly, you gotta stay.
The fact that you feel, you feel like you joined Psyche's panel, like, in fact they're even up here, I mean.
Well psyche, that's almost anyone joined so that's fine
But you just got to feed how many how many times it's a second Alex IPP to him a hundred and like
22 times to like fucking like six times. You just don't know what the fuck you're talking about
So I guess this guy disrespecting the
Did you just say that we're stupid everybody who listens to psyche I don't know if you thought that's like no I said I said you guys were
No, I didn't say everyone. No, I didn't say you guys are you guys definitely are retarded and you guys know
Well, if it's the exception doesn't make the rule so if there's like a hundred people that listen to Psyche
The 10 of them are retarded. I'm gonna call them retarded, but the exception doesn't make the rule
Not I wasn't you're not even see that's you too stupid to hear the argument
You know, we always roll together, you know, you're too stupid to even hear the argument. That's how retarded you are
Why are you up here? What do you want with me? Why are you talking to me by the way and page and not with guess who's the fucking
room out of the room
that the guys can't, this guy can't read the rule.
Go listen to the fucking retort.
The exception doesn't make the rule, though.
You understand that, right?
Can you go back on it to Summer's community?
Can you, would you like me to explain,
dude, I'll be friendly and explain it to you.
That's all friendly.
Yeah, go back there, go back there.
Go back to the talk here.
All right, I'll explain it one more time for you.
We can accept pipes.
We accept pipes over you.
No, you can accept pipes.
I can explain the exception doesn't make the rule.
So if you have like...
Yeah, a hundred people you can put thousand whatever you want to make if you have like a hundred people
Ten of them are dumb dumb what you have a hundred people will listen to me just ask me to explain to you and I'm
Watch explain if you know
Do we have to explain to this guy that we don't want to fuck with him? I don't know well you're the pin
You're the exception to the rule
Yeah, we don't want to fuck with you. There's 90 other people though. What about that? You're pissing off page
Let me tell you that if you get her mad that says a lot. Yeah, look at her fucking give a fuck
She's welcome to join in explain why she's mad and we can talk. I'm not gonna try to debate
You know what the exception doesn't make the rule. I don't give a fuck and giving you dude
You're making one person at the exception does it make the rule?
Come back face
One person's mad
Out of a hundred I mean it doesn't
Channel she's a co-host of this channel
I mean you'd have to talk to psyche about that pretty sure. She's not I don't know for a sure
Okay, well you came up here trying to fucking debate and talk shit, but now you realize that you realize
No, it's like you tell me to shut up. I'll be quiet you jumped on something you couldn't handle
Please tell him to shut up. Please save me psyche psyche. Save me. Save me. Yeah, don't fucking know
Well, here's my problem. Let me one more thing be and I will be one more thing though
Don't jump up on here one more thing before I be quiet
Well, you can just shut up one more thing before I be quiet
You jump up on here trying to fucking like jump on me and like fucking debate shit
Fucking and then after I put your ass up you're asking for help from psyche. So don't jump up here trying to talk to you
You know better word because I love it. It's my favorite word
But yeah, I know
Fuck off, you know what my favorite effort is
Help me psyche help me psyche help me. Yeah, that's a good argument psyche help me
So it's like me asking for like Andrew. Help me Andrew. Help me. Oh fuck. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh
You know what? Very good logical argument, ma'am a very good argument
You've been making them all night. You know what? I'll get down and kiss your ass because you've been making such a good argument all night
Your ghost you really let me kiss the dum-dums ask you because you guys are such
You put them on your you know ghost you really know how to dry a woman's pussy ever
A thousand percent I'm literally holding back right now because I feel like I'm like bullying people
So I'm just gonna be cool from now on because you guys don't know what the fuck you're doing. Are you okay?
When I talk to you, it's like we're in a different level. It's like if I'm a if I'm a trained fighter
Another man that's smaller than me. You just know how to fight. Yeah, it's a disadvantage
Thank you, Bob
If it was my if I did have influence on psyche, none of you would be up here
I don't have influence. It's his fucking. It's his
You're saying you want to be Hitler?
what the fuck are you even what a fucking retarded thing to say you're talking
about manipulating people in the control you're too stupid to have the car you
don't know what the fuck you're talking about you don't talk about go ahead and
explain it then
Damn, you know, you're staying that if you had influence over psyche, which you probably wish he did
None of us would be here. So you're basically saying you want to control and manipulate people
Goddamn retards get along god damn no never once said that the burden of you made the claim
Which I didn't bring the proof is on you
Never once said that
I mean, that's fine.
Yeah, what's the exception?
Exemption nothing you mean exception. I gotta make your argument for you. I'm tired of doing it. I'm working against my soul
Yeah, I gotta help you guys out
I
Literally have to help you guys out give a gym membership
What is he gonna say good times give me a heads up?
It'll just make some random insult and then people understand what he's saying and that's what I'm guessing
Thank You good times
No, I literally have to I've literally argued it's myself like I literally have to make your argument for you
Are you saying you're not retarded
Okay, you shut the fuck up. How about that right night? She's not gonna sleep with you fucking simp. Yeah
Yeah
This is fucking easy boy
Okay, how am I retarded well, well you're like you said it how am I retarded is your fat
What is an insult when you say dum-dum? Yeah, like what is an insult?
Yeah, what is an insult when you say dum-dum like I said in cell, but you met and saw that's fucking stupid
You are I gotta fucking make your argument for you
There you go. I mean to go just for saying shut up. That's not a good argument
Nah, I could have said it the way that he said it
But I just thought it was funnier the way that I said it so you can be a dumb
She don't know what the fuck you're talking about. I've been saying that for an hour
Thank you. Get this guy out of here, brother
No, he's gonna get me out of here
Good try though
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
No, not yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Can you please repeat what the fuck? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're a fucking idiot
You're trying to say one versus three don't try to fight anybody, right?
Oh my god, not dumb dumb, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god
Mean you guys don't know what the fuck you're talking about
Honestly, I'm trying to be me. Let's get to that. I'm just clear that up real quick
I'm not trying to be mean
I'll give you know what I'll all of ranch all three of you because I know she's not gonna take it
But I'll advance both of you dudes
What the fuck you're talking about let's just say it's okay, let's all get along would you
I don't accept it. I don't know you
I don't know you
You don't know what the fuck
This is about as dumb as it gets just concede this concede. Thank you. Good time
Well, well Chris will have fun talk to you're not gonna concede. I'm going back to my you're gonna leave aren't you you're gonna leave, aren't you?
Well, I leave aren't you I don't think you're you lose
You're annoying didn't you leave you lose you never won one argument you're gonna be hey listen for your audience when one
At least when one before you angry and annoyed good times come on
And you leave me with her
Crystal
Hello
No, well you're gonna have to restart your shit if you want to go again. They all quit. Sorry
Sorry, I mean it's like I put my family kid again, but yeah, they come back
Back in yeah, that's a good point brother. Yeah, you can put your link back
When I'm here, I need to pin it but
Yeah, you know what I
Need to pin the link
Well, I thought you said something different brother
Hey, by the way, so I can leave I didn't mean to disrespect your pan
I didn't hear you say anything wrong
Kept your legs. Yeah
Yeah, didn't even come in
Damon knows
You know, he knows he knows that a lot he
And by the way everyone that's listening for psyches panel by the way like pay anyone that's listening
We don't have to debate when I argue well me personally weakness hang out. That's his panel. It's not mine
We don't have to debate
So I'm sorry to make it like that, but we miss all hang out
No, we don't have to argue
What are you debating about? Oh wolf man. What's up? What's going on?
What we were debating about
Debating on a fucking thing. I was just in the chat. I just keep getting signed out. That's all
How you doing with man?
Chilling by the way, is that a correct? Is that the correct way to call you?
Did
But yeah, like I said, I keep talking about stuff
Well, if you see where they're gonna make a new
Dracula, I didn't know that I don't know. Yeah, I just watched the fucking trailer for it. Yeah
That's like Gary old man like I was gonna say neo
Yeah, they're making a new one
Is it Keanu Reeves?
No, no, no, no, it's all a new calf. I
Think Keanu Reeves he just was in ballerina. I think they're gonna make another John Wick
Hmm, are they really gonna use a fucking make another John Wick movie?
Yeah, and his ass is gonna be in there
that's gonna turn out to be a boy. He's old as fuck now, but if he was younger that'd be like a fucking
Mission impossible John Wick. I mean keep making them
Yeah, sassy scarlet and ever said that by the way
You're crying the psych. Okay. You got you got timed up and you broke the rules
Okay, I'm more you call people
Why are you talking to you so you complain in the psych is not gonna do but who are you talking to you?
The rules you kind of psyched. Who's he talking to man? You're a loser. Oh my gosh. Who are you talking to?
Yeah, because you broke the rules. I asked your mom. You don't understand how to answer a fucking simple question
Who are you talking to one of the best? I'm a ghost
I'm a psyche
Yo, you're a loser. You're talking to you don't you don't know there's niggas like are you we got another
Bitch let's run that motherfucker
You're let's run that bitch
Yeah, I know what's going on.
Who are you talking to?
You dumb fuck.
What am I doing?
Are you too stupid even to understand who you're talking to?
Stupid motherfucker.
I can't hear you.
Simple fucking question.
Who are you talking to?
Jesus.
I got back up later.
You heard something.
I got it.
Go.
Let's let's make a job. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
You're too fucking stupid to answer a question. All right, I'm big on
Who are you talking to
This dude is too fucking stupid
Thank you
Sike psych see when rain apologize when rain apologize for calling me a PDF. I didn't accept it
See when you don't set these
His girlfriend
Who are you talking to, bitch?
No one understands it.
Who are you talking to, dumb dumb?
Who are you talking to?
I'm gonna crash the fuck out.
Then why are you here if you're not talking to anyone?
You're just talking to talk?
Dumb dumb.
Hey, you don't know what the fuck are you talking to you?
Oh, I got rain.
I
Are you talking to
Yeah
For the chat
Why are you still talking we still don't know what the fuck
I'm sure you can mess
Hey
You're not gonna shut up
Hey Sam, can you tell everyone why you're a beautiful
Great question. All right. Bye, bitch. Fuck off. You're not going to be you made the claim
or enough proofs on you. You're not going to make it. Bye, bitch.
Fucking mouth, you fucking piece of shit. You fucking retard it.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll put it on. You know what?
I'll put it on for them. So, you're not very talkative.
I'm just listening. I'm just watching. I'm just listening. You watching your chat.
I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I'm just I
Well, okay
I saw I saw a bunch of people in the chat like making like little like word jokes and putting people's names and
On the panel
Oh, I'm typing that bitch. Oh, I say you're heard